Press Gang Printers fonds
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
- Printing samples, 1970 - 1993; F-134-6; 1.64 m of graphic material 32 photographs 13 printing plates; Physical description: 15 photographs located in F-134-6-2-0-29 Physical description: 2 photographs located in F-134-6-4-0-32 Physical description: 1 photograph located in F-134-6-4-0-110 Physical 
  - Publications, 1971 - 1992; F-134-6-4; 1.07 m of textual records 1.07 m of graphic material 17 photographs
    - Vancouver Status of Women: Pornography and Prostitution, 1981; F-134-6-4-0-154 (Archival box - standard 134-25)
    - Vancouver Women's Bookstore, 1977 - 1982; F-134-6-4-0-155 (Archival box - standard 134-25)
    - Vancouver Women's Bookstore: Catalogue, 1973; F-134-6-4-0-156 (Newspaper box 134-32)
      - Vancouver Women's Bookstore Catalog, October 1973; F-134-6-4-0-156-1 (Newspaper box 134-32)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item232.
    - Vancouver Women's Health Collective: Birth Control for Immigrant Women, 1987; F-134-6-4-0-157 (Archival box - standard 134-25)
    - Vancouver Women's Health Collective: Wicca, 1975; F-134-6-4-0-158 (Newspaper box 134-32)
      - Wicca: Newsletter of the Women's Health Movement in B.C., vol. 1 no. 6, April 1975; F-134-6-4-0-158-1 (Newspaper box 134-32)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item233.
    - Vancouver Women's Study Group: Women and Socialism: Accounting for Our Experience, 1979; F-134-6-4-0-159 (Archival box - standard 134-25)
    - Vancouver YWCA: Women Running Newsletter, 1979 - 1980; F-134-6-4-0-160 (Newspaper box 134-32)
      - Vancouver Women Running: YWCA Newsletter, 1979; F-134-6-4-0-160-1 (Newspaper box 134-32)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item234.
      - Vancouver Women Running: YWCA Newsletter, 1980; F-134-6-4-0-160-2 (Newspaper box 134-32)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item235.
      - Vancouver Women Running: YWCA Newsletter, 1980; F-134-6-4-0-160-3 (Newspaper box 134-32)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item236.
    - Victoria Community School: Wanna Know Somethin'?, 1974; F-134-6-4-0-161 (Archival box - standard 134-25)
    - Victoria Women's Centre and Transition House - photographs, 1974; F-134-6-4-0-162 (Archival box - small 134-33)
    - [Vietnam], 1972; F-134-6-4-0-163 (Archival box - standard 134-25)
    - Vuskovic, Pedro: Latin America: The Way Forward … Fascism or Socialism?, 1976; F-134-6-4-0-164 (Archival box - standard 134-25)
    - Walton, Jen: The Treeplanter's Daily Record Book, 1990; F-134-6-4-0-165 (Archival box - standard 134-25)
    - Watno Dur: The Literary Monthly Magazine of Punjabi, 1973 - 1974; F-134-6-4-0-166 (Newspaper box 134-32)
      - The Watno Dur: The Literary Monthly Magazine of Panjabi, vol. 1 no. 3, September 1973; F-134-6-4-0-166-1 (Newspaper box 134-32)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item237.
      - The Watno Dur: The Literary Monthly Magazine of Panjabi, vol. 1 no. 3, September 1973; F-134-6-4-0-166-2 (Newspaper box 134-32)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item238.
      - The Watno Dur: The Literary Monthly Magazine of Panjabi, vol. 1 no. 4, October 1973; F-134-6-4-0-166-3 (Newspaper box 134-32)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item239.
      - The Watno Dur: The Literary Monthly Magazine of Panjabi, vol. 1 no. 5, November 1973; F-134-6-4-0-166-4 (Newspaper box 134-32)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item240.
      - The Watno Dur: The Literary Monthly Magazine of Panjabi, vol. 1 no. 6, December 1973; F-134-6-4-0-166-5 (Newspaper box 134-32)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item241.
      - The Watno Dur: The Literary Monthly Magazine of Panjabi, vol. 1 no. 10, April 1974; F-134-6-4-0-166-6 (Newspaper box 134-32)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item242.
    - Wawaw Free Press, 1974; F-134-6-4-0-167 (Newspaper box 134-32)
      - WAWAW Free Press, vol. 1, 1974; F-134-6-4-0-167-1 (Newspaper box 134-32)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item243.
    - West, David: Picking Up the Pieces, 1989; F-134-6-4-0-168 (Archival box - standard 134-25)
    - Wild West Organic Harvest Co-op, April 1982; F-134-6-4-0-169 (Archival box - standard 134-25)
    - Witchwords (magazine), 1989; F-134-6-4-0-170 (Archival box - standard 134-25)
    - Women Against Imperialism: Women in El Salvador, 1982; F-134-6-4-0-171 (Archival box - standard 134-26)
    - Women Against Violence Against Women: Information for the Sexually Assaulted, 1984; F-134-6-4-0-172 (Archival box - standard 134-26)
    - Women and Economic Development, 1980; F-134-6-4-0-173 (Archival box - standard 134-26)
    - Women and the Economy: Building our Own Agenda, November 1986; F-134-6-4-0-174 (Archival box - standard 134-26)
    - Women in Celebration: Networking Directory, 1988; F-134-6-4-0-175 (Archival box - standard 134-26)
    - Women in Focus Production and Distribution Centre: Catalogues, 1977 - 1982; F-134-6-4-0-176 (Archival box - standard 134-26)
    - Women Rally for Action, 1976; F-134-6-4-0-177 (Archival box - standard 134-26)
    - Women's Access Manual, Langley-Abbotsford, 1974; F-134-6-4-0-178 (Newspaper box 134-32)
      - Women's Access Manual: Langley-Abbotsford, 1974; F-134-6-4-0-178-1 (Newspaper box 134-32)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item244.
      - Women's Access Manual: Langley-Abbotsford, 1974; F-134-6-4-0-178-2 (Newspaper box 134-32)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item245.
    - Women's Economic Agenda, 1987 - 1988; F-134-6-4-0-179 (Archival box - standard 134-26)
    - Women's Research Centre, 1988 - 1989; F-134-6-4-0-180 (Archival box - standard 134-26)
    - Women's Skills Development Centre, 1986 - 1987; F-134-6-4-0-181 (Archival box - standard 134-26)
    - Women's Work Directory, 1979; F-134-6-4-0-182 (Archival box - standard 134-26)
    - Working Group on Sexual Violence: The Pornography Paper, 1986; F-134-6-4-0-183 (Archival box - standard 134-26)
    - Working Women's Association: Working in Hospitals, 1973; F-134-6-4-0-184 (Archival box - standard 134-26)
    - Wyss, Barbara and Teressa Nahanee: Inter-Tribal Cookbook (Recipes of North American Indians: Traditional and Modern), 1982; F-134-6-4-0-185 (Archival box - standard 134-26)
- Promotion, marketing and fundraising files, 1977 - 1992; F-134-7; 9 cm of textual records
  Series consists of records relating to Press Gang Printer's promotion, marketing and fundraising activities. Activities, events and topics documented include advertising, fundraising events and auctions. Records include advertising copy, promotional material, correspondence, and donation records.
  - Advertising, 1984; F-134-7-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 134-16)
  - Advertising, 1985 - 1990; F-134-7-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 134-16)
  - Advertising, 1989 - 1990; F-134-7-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 134-16)
  - Auction, 1992; F-134-7-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 134-16)
  - Donations, 1992; F-134-7-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 134-16)
  - Press Gang ad ideas, [198-?]; F-134-7-0-0-6
  - Promotional material, vol. 1, 1977 - 1992; F-134-7-0-0-7 (Archival box - standard 134-16)
  - Promotional material, vol. 2, 1977 - 1992; F-134-7-0-0-8 (Archival box - standard 134-16)
  - Publishing Collective - publicity, [198-?]; F-134-7-0-0-9 (Archival box - standard 134-16)
  - Shaggy Horse Fundraiser, 1992; F-134-7-0-0-10 (Archival box - standard 134-16)
  - Stay at Home Fundraiser, 1992; F-134-7-0-0-11 (Archival box - standard 134-16)
- British Columbia Federation of Women (BCFW) files, 1977 - 1988; F-134-8; 25 cm of textual records; British Columbia Federation of Women
  The British Columbia Federation of Women (BCFW) was founded in 1974 as an umbrella group of women's organizations. Its objective was to bring about women's liberation through fundamental social change, providing a provincial network of support, information- and resource-sharing, and coordinated action. Groups joined as affiliate members and were organized into regional units; federation-wide matters were overseen by the Coordinating Collective, several standing committees (Finance, Communications and Convention), and various ad hoc committees established to address specific issues and projects. At the Annual General Convention delegates from each of the regions elected committee members and voted on policy resolutions. The BCFW disbanded in 1989.
  This series consists of records relating to Press Gang Printer's participation in the BCFW as a member organization. Activities, events and topics documented include policy development, meetings of the Coordinating Collective, committees, and the Lower Mainland Region section, BCFW conventions, and liaison with other member groups. Records include correspondence, agendas, meeting minutes and supporting papers, conference material, publications and other reference material, grant applications, and briefs and reports.
  For other material relating to the BCFW, see also the following finding aids: Simon Fraser Student Society Women's Centre fonds (F-40), series 7; Working Women Unite fonds (F-45), series 2; Ellen Frank fonds (F-82), series 2; Women's Bookstore collection (F-111), series 5.
  - BCFW Convention, 1977; F-134-8-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 134-27)
  - BCFW Convention, 1979; F-134-8-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 134-27)
  - BCFW Convention - observer packet, 1979; F-134-8-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 134-27)
  - BCFW Convention, 1981 - 1982; F-134-8-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 134-27)
  - BCFW Convention, 1982 - 1983; F-134-8-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 134-27)
  - BCFW Convention, 1983 - 1984; F-134-8-0-0-6 (Archival box - standard 134-27)
  - BCFW Newsletters, 1977 - 1980; F-134-8-0-0-7 (Archival box - standard 134-27)
  - Brief to the Royal Commission on the Incarceration of Female Offenders, 1977; F-134-8-0-0-8 (Archival box - standard 134-27)
  - Constitution and policy handbook, 1977; F-134-8-0-0-9 (Archival box - standard 134-27)
  - Coordinating Collective, 1982; F-134-8-0-0-10 (Archival box - standard 134-27)
  - Coordinating Collective, 1982 - 1988; F-134-8-0-0-11 (Archival box - standard 134-27)
  - Coordinating Collective, 1983; F-134-8-0-0-12 (Archival box - standard 134-27)
  - Correspondence, 1977 - 1981; F-134-8-0-0-13 (Archival box - standard 134-27)
  - Correspondence, 1978 - 1979; F-134-8-0-0-14 (Archival box - standard 134-27)
  - General, 1977 - 1981; F-134-8-0-0-15 (Archival box - standard 134-28)
  - General, 1977 - 1982; F-134-8-0-0-16 (Archival box - standard 134-28)
  - General, 1978 - 1979; F-134-8-0-0-17 (Archival box - standard 134-28)
  - General, 1978 - 1980; F-134-8-0-0-18 (Archival box - standard 134-28)
  - General, 1983 - 1984; F-134-8-0-0-19 (Archival box - standard 134-28)
  - General, 1984; F-134-8-0-0-20 (Archival box - standard 134-28)
  - Grant applications, 1982 - 1983; F-134-8-0-0-21 (Archival box - standard 134-28)
  - Grant applications, 1983; F-134-8-0-0-22 (Archival box - standard 134-28)
  - Lower Mainland Regional Meeting, 1982; F-134-8-0-0-23 (Archival box - standard 134-28)
  - Lower Mainland Regional Meeting, 1983 - 1984; F-134-8-0-0-24 (Archival box - standard 134-28)
  - Reference publications, 1982 - 1984; F-134-8-0-0-25 (Newspaper box 134-32)
    - SWAG: Status of Women News, vol. 11 no. 2, April 1984; F-134-8-0-0-25-1 (Newspaper box 134-32)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item246.
    - Communiqu'elles, vol. 10 no. 2, March 1984; F-134-8-0-0-25-2 (Newspaper box 134-32)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item247.
    - Alberta Status of Women Action Committee, vol. 5 no. 3, April 1984; F-134-8-0-0-25-3 (Newspaper box 134-32)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item248.
    - Images: Kootenay Women's Paper, vol. 9 no. 10, March 1982; F-134-8-0-0-25-4 (Newspaper box 134-32)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item249.
  - Regional discussion, 1983; F-134-8-0-0-26 (Archival box - standard 134-28)
  - Reports and working papers, 1981 - 1983; F-134-8-0-0-27 (Archival box - standard 134-28)
  - Rights of Lesbians, 1983; F-134-8-0-0-28 (Archival box - standard 134-28)
  - Standing Committee, 1979; F-134-8-0-0-29 (Archival box - standard 134-28)
  - Women Against Violence Against Woment - Rape Relief, 1982 - 1983; F-134-8-0-0-30 (Archival box - standard 134-28)
  - Women and pensions conference, 1983; F-134-8-0-0-31 (Archival box - standard 134-28)